Matin Kahrizi

Summary

I'm a Front-End web developer who enjoys designing and creating wonderful products. I started this journey about 3 years ago and I believe there is no limitations for me to learn new things.

My main expertise is React JS and I daily use React, Webpack, Tailwind Css and Material UI in my projects

Work Experience

Tafarda - 05/2021 to 03/2022 **Tehran**, Iran

- At Tafarda company, I was the main Front end developer and we were working on Iranian and European web applications.
- One of the latest applications that we launched, Is called Rsoon.
- In this company I managed to upgrade my knowledge in terms of React also I learned Agile and Scrum systems

Liteweb - 02/2020 to 06/2021 **Tehran**, Iran

- At Liteweb company, I was one of the Front end developers and we were working on Freelance projects
- In this company I managed to level-up my JavaScript skills also I learned how to work with Laravel project's structure

Education

MSc in Computer Science at Shamsipour Technical College (2021- present)
BSc in Computer Science Shamsipour Technical College (2019- 2021)



Contact

+98 937 898 5651

https://matinkahrizi@gmail.com
https://www.github.com/maricolR

Projects

 You can see all of my projects and access their source code in my website at <u>Here</u>